（忆往昔）
我想爸爸想让我们继续他的工作
I think he wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔 家族事业
Saving people, hunting things. Family business.
我真的不明白为什么你就如此相信他
I don't understand the blind faith you have in the man.
做儿子的本应如此
It's called being a good son.
你快点给我消失 你再也无法控制我了
You were just pissed off you couldn't control me anymore!
要是你的儿子们能知道爸爸是多么爱他们
If only your boys knew how much their daddy loved them.
爸爸
Dad?
- 他有跟你说过什么吗 - 没有
- Did he say anything to you? - No.
我在追查爸爸的死因
I'm dealing with Dad's death.
那你呢
Are you?
（现在）
（红洛奇 蒙大纳）
[邪恶力量 第2季第3集]
哇 你听听她的歌
Woo! Listen to her purr.
你会觉得从来没有 听到过如此甜美的声音
You ever heard anything so sweet?
如果你对唱这歌的这妞有兴趣 直接跟我说就得了
If you two wanna get a room, just let me know.
哦 宝贝 别理他
Oh, don't listen to him, baby.
他根本不了解我们的感觉
He doesn't understand us.
- 你看上去心情不错啊 - 为什么我得心情不好
- You're in a good mood. - Why shouldn't I be?
- 没什么 - 我现在有车
- No reason. - I got my car.
又有事做 一切看上去都还不错
Got a case. Things are looking up.
得了吧
Wow.
你只不过是听说有些牛 还有人离奇死亡而已
Give you a couple of severed heads and a pile of dead cows…
就乐成这傻样
and you're Mr. Sunshine.
离红客栈市还有多远
How far to Red Lodge?
大概还有300里
About another 300 miles.
很好
Good.
凶杀案的调查正在进行 我只能告诉你们这些
The murder investigation is ongoing. That's all I can share with the press.
是的 是的 我们理解 我们只是来记录事实
Sure, we understand that. But just for the record.
是你上周发现了第一具断头尸体
You found the first head last week…
- 是吗 - 嗯
- …correct? - Uh - huh.
还有接下来的那名叫 克里斯蒂娜·福来明的女子的尸体
Okay, and the other, a Christina Flanagan.
- 那是两天前的事 - 然后…
- That was two days ago. Then…
噢 谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
抱歉 伙计们 时间到了 我们就说到这里吧
Sorry, Boys.time's up. We're done here.
最后一个问题
One last question.
- 那些牛又是怎么回事 - 你说什么
- What about the cattle? - Excuse me?
最近有发现很多牛离奇死亡
The cows found dead…
伤口撕裂 却没有血液
split open, drained, over a dozen cases?
那又怎么样
What about them?
那你不觉得这些之间有关联吗
So you don't think there's a connection?
关联到…
Connection with…?
最早的那些死掉的牛和
First, cattle mutilations.
现在的两起谋杀案 有点象是某些祭祀仪式
Now, two murders. Kind of sounds like ritual stuff.
就象是祭魔仪式
You know, like satanic cult ritual stuff.
你…
You…
- 你们不是在开玩笑吧 - 当然不是
- You're not kidding. - No.
根本就没有牛被故意杀掉这回事
Those cows aren't being mutilated.
- 你想知道我是怎么知道的吗 - 你怎么知道
- You wanna know how I know? - How?
这根本不可能是故意的
Because there's no such thing as cattle mutilation.
如果牛白天死了
Cow drops, leave it in the sun…
在48个小时之内 它的血液肯定会流干
within 48 hours the bloat will split it open so clean…
这是基本的外科常识
it's just about surgical.
内脏里的血会流到地上 被土壤吸收掉
The bodily fluids fall down into the ground, get soaked up…
因为有地心引力
because that's what gravity does.
嘿 但是传说恶魔也做同样的事
But, hey, it could be Satan.
你们刚才说为哪家报纸干活来着
What newspaper did you say you work for?
- 世界周刊 - 世界周刊
- World Weekly News. - Weekly World News.
- 世界 - 世界周刊
- World - Weekly World.
世界 我是新来的
World I'm new.
给我滚出去
Get out of my office.
- 约翰 - 杰夫
- John. - Jeff.
杰夫 恩 我知道
Jeff, I know that.
考特医生要你现在就去他的办公室
Dr. Dworkin needs to see you in his office.
但他不是正在度假吗
But Dr. Dworkings on vacation.
他回来了 而且正在气头上 他吵着叫你过去
He's back and he's pissed. He's screaming for you.
如果换了我是你 我就…
So if I were you, I would…
那好吧
Okay.
那些在佛罗里达的恶魔
Those Satanists in Florida
他们会在牺牲的祭品上做记号 不是吗
they marked their victims?
没错 前额上会有个倒五角星
Yeah. Reverse pentacle on the forehead.
看来佛罗里达发生的案子还真不少啊
So much F'd up crap happens in Florida.
来 打开它
All right, open it.
你来开
You open it.
你这个懦夫
You wuss.
没有五角星的标记
Well, no pentagram.
- 可怜的女孩 - 也许我们应该看看她的嘴里
- Wow. Poor girl. - Maybe we should look in her mouth.
看看她喉咙里是不是有什么古怪的东西
See if those wackos stuffed anything down her throat.
也许就象 沉默的羔羊 一样
You know, kind of like the moth in Silence of the Lambs.
- 那试试看吧 - 这次该你来干了
- Yeah, yeah, go ahead. - No, you go ahead.
- 你说什么 - 这好象并没那么难吧
- What? - Put the lotion in the basket.
得了 我承认是胆小鬼好了吧
Right, yeah, I'm the wuss, huh?
真麻烦
Whatever.
- 迪恩 给我一个桶 - 找到什么了吗
- Dean, get me a bucket. - Find something?
没有 我要吐了
No, I'm gonna puke.
- 等等 再把她的嘴弄开看看 - 什么
- Wait, lift her lip up again. - What?
- 你是不是想让我吐出来 - 没有 我好象看到了些东西
- You want me to throw up. - No, no, no. I think I saw something.
那是不是有个洞
What is that, a hole?
- 那是牙齿 - 萨姆 那是獠牙
- It's a tooth. - Sam, that's a fang.
平时藏着的吸血鬼的獠牙 你这是在开玩笑吧
A retractable set of vampire fangs. You gotta be kidding me.
看来事情有些复杂了
Well, this changes things.
不是吗
You think?
- 最近怎么样 - 生活象梦那么美好
- How's it going? - Living the dream.
- 你想要点什么 - 两杯啤酒 谢谢
- What can I get for you? - Two beers, please.
我们想要找人
So we're looking for some people.
我知道 单身的滋味不好过
Sure. It's hard to be lonely.
的确 但我不是那个意思
Yeah, but that's not what I meant.
很好 这些人应该搬到这里不到6个月
Great, so these people, they would've moved here about six months ago.
- 可能比较粗暴 喜欢喝酒 - 都是些夜猫子
- Probably pretty rowdy, like to drink. - Yeah, real night owls, you know?
白天睡觉 晚上出来狂欢
Sleep all day, party all night.
巴克农场前些日子被租了出去 大赚了一笔
Barker Farm got leased out a couple months ago. Real winners.
那些人常到这里喝酒 吵杂的很
They've been in here a lot. Drinkers. Noisy.
我有警告过他们一两次
I've had to eighty six them once or twice.
谢了
Thanks.
- 张开你的嘴 - 你说什么
- Smile. - What?
- 让我们看看你的牙齿 - 为…
- Show us those pearly whites. - For the love of
你得相信我不是你们想找的 我不是吸血鬼
You wanna stick that thing someplace else? I'm not a vampire.
那好 我说实话 我在酒吧听见你们说的话
Yeah, that's right. I heard you guys.
- 你还知道关于吸血鬼的其他事吗 - 杀掉它们的方法
- What do you know about vampires? - How to kill them.
老实说 这刀子真的让我不爽
Now, seriously, bro, that knife's making me itch.
- 嘿 - 放轻松 伙计
- Hey. - Whoa, easy there, Chachi.
看见了吗 没有吸血鬼的牙齿吧 可以放过我了吗
See? Fangless. Happy?
你们到底是谁
Now, who the hell are you?
萨姆·温彻斯特和迪恩·温彻斯特
Sam and Dean Winchester.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
我见过你们的父亲 真是个了不起的猎人
I met your old man once. Hell of a guy. Great hunter.
我听说他死了 我很遗憾
I heard he passed. I'm sorry.
真可惜
That's big shoes.
但我又听说你们俩继承了他的事业
But from what I hear, you guys fill them. Great trackers.
也是了不起的猎人
Good in a tight spot.
- 看来你们很了解我们家族 - 消息传的很快
- Seem to know a lot about our family. - Word travels fast.
你们知道猎人之间是怎么说起你们家族的吗
You know how hunters talk.
我们不知道
No, we don't, actually.
我想大概你们父亲没有告诉你们过
I guess there's a lot your dad never told you, huh?
那就是说
So, um…
这两个吸血鬼 都是你在盯着吗
So those two vampires, they were yours.
是的 两周前他们来到这里
Yep. Been here two weeks.
- 你有去看过那巴克农场吗 - 那里只不过是一群嬉皮士
- Did you check out that farm? - Just a bunch of hippie freaks.
他们的那股味道能杀了你
They could kill you with that patchouli smell.
吸血鬼的老巢在哪里呢
Where's the nest, then?
我一直藏着这些东西
I got this one covered.
别误会 见到你们我很高兴
Don't get me wrong, it's a real pleasure meeting you.
我追这些家伙有一年了
But I've been on this thing for over a year.
我在奥斯汀杀了一个吸血鬼 追踪到了这里的巢穴
I killed a fang back in Austin, tracked the nest here.
我会结束这些家伙
I'll finish it.
- 我们能帮你 - 谢谢
- We could help. - Thanks.
但我比较喜欢一个人干
But I'm a go it alone type of guy.
我也希望能够参与其中
Come on, I've been itching for a hunt.
很抱歉 但我听说两州之外有个卓帕卡布拉
Sorry. But, hey, I hear there's a chupacabra two states over.
你们可以去那看看
Go ahead and knock yourselves out.
见到你们真的很高兴
It was real good meeting you, though.
办完事后 我请你们喝酒
I'll buy you a drink on the flip side.
看来我非得请你们喝酒不可了
So I guess I gotta buy you that drink.
你去哪
Here you go.
不 不 我来请客 别这样
No, no, I got it. Come on.
不 我要请你们
No I insist.
- 谢谢 宝贝 - 不客气 谢谢
- Thank you, sweetie. - You're welcome. Thanks.
- 又一个恶魔归于尘土 - 是的
- Another one bites the dust. - That's right.
迪恩
Dean.
伙计 你给那混蛋理了个新发型
You gave that big ass fang one hell of a haircut, my friend.
- 谢谢你 - 那还真不赖啊 绝对不赖
Thank you. - That was beautiful, absolutely beautiful.
- 是啊 你还好吗 萨姆 - 我还好
- Well… You all right, Sammy? - Yeah, I'm fine.
- 还好 放轻松点 萨姆 - 只有他能那么称呼我
- Well, lighten up a little, Sammy. - He's the one who gets to call me that.
不好意思 没别的意思 只是想庆祝一下 这次干的不错
Okay. No offense meant. Just celebrating a little. Job well done.
是的 但我没想要把他的头锯掉 这也不值得庆祝
Right, well, decapitations aren't my idea of a good time, I guess.
哦 伙计 他不是人 别那样斤斤计较了
Oh, come on, man. It's not like it was human.
- 你得找点乐子 - 这话我早就和他说过
- You gotta have fun with your job. - That's what I've been trying to tell him.
你得向他学学
You could learn a thing or two from this guy.
我想我会的
Yeah, I bet I could.
听着 我不陪你们玩了
Look, I'm not gonna bring you guys down.
我得回旅馆了
I'm just gonna go back to the motel.
你确定
Are you sure?
萨姆
Sammy.
记得来接我 好吗
Remind me to beat that buzz kill out of you later, all right?
- 我说错话了吗 - 没有 他有时就那样
- Something I said? - No, he just gets that way sometimes.
说你呢
Tell you what…
该你喝了
match of Quarters for the next round.
我捡起弓朝那丑鬼射去
So I pick up this crossbow, and I hit that ugly sucker…
镶银的箭正中它的心脏
with a silver - tipped arrow right in his heart.
萨姆 那时正呆在车子里
Sammy's waiting in the car…
我和我父亲把那怪物拖进森林里
and me and my dad take the thing into the woods…
烧掉了他
and burn it to a crisp.
我就坐在哪里 看着那堆大火
I'm sitting there, and I'm looking into the fire. I'm thinking to myself:
我就在想 我才16岁
"I'm 16 years old.
象我年纪的孩子都还在担心考试什么的
Kids my age are worried about pimples, prom dates.
而我这样的生活
I'm seeing things that they'll never even know.
他们可能想都没想到过
Never even dream of."
- 所以那时 我真的 - 从没享受过童年吗
- So right then, I just sort of - Embraced the life?
- 没错 - 真惨
- Yeah. - Yeah.
是啊
Yeah.
你什么时候开始猎鬼的
How'd you get started?
我第一次看到吸血鬼时 我才18岁
First time I saw a vampire, I was barely 18.
就我和我妹妹在家
Home alone with my sister.
我听见她房间的窗户破了
I hear the window break in her room.
我拿了我父亲的枪 跑进去 想赶走它
I grab my dad's gun, run in. Try to get it off her.
但太晚了
It was too late.
所以我开枪射了它
So I shoot the damn thing…
当然这对它来说 就象隔靴搔痒
which is about as useful as snapping it with a rubber band.
它转向我 把我抓起来
It rushes me, picks me up, flings me across the room…
把我扔到了房间的另一头 我昏了过去
knocks me out cold.
当我醒来的时候
When I wake up…
那吸血鬼已经走了
the vampire's gone…
我妹妹也死了
my sister is gone.
然后呢
And then?
然后…
Then…
我把那消息告诉了你的父亲
Try explaining that one to your family.
我离开家…
So I left home.
到处找关于它的信息
And then bummed around, looking for information.
关于你们是如何追踪它们 如何杀了它们的
How you track them, how you kill them.
而后我找到了那个吸血鬼
And I found that fang.
这是我第一次猎鬼
It was my first kill.
听到你妹妹的事我很遗憾
Sorry about your sister.
没事
Yeah.
她很漂亮
She was beautiful.
我仍然能看得到她 即使她不在了
I can still see her, you know? The way she was.
这是很久以前的事了
But, hey, that was a long time ago.
我得说 你爸爸
I mean, your dad.
他走的太快了
It's gotta be rough.
是啊
Yeah.
他是猎鬼者中的最勇敢的一个
Yeah, you know, he was just one of those guys.
即使身处险境
Took some terrible beatings…
也会勇往直前
and just kept coming.
所以我常对自己说
So you're always saying to yourself, you know:
他是无所不能的 他就在我们身边
"He's indestructible. He'll always be around.
没什么能够杀了我的父亲
Nothing can kill my dad."
那就象…
And just like that…
他去远行了
he's gone.
我对萨姆不能这样说
I can't talk about this to Sammy.
我得装成没什么事一样
You know, I gotta keep my game face on.
但是…
But, uh…
事实上 我掩饰地的并不怎么好
But the truth is, I'm not handling it very well.
- 我感觉就象 - 内心有个黑洞
- Feel like I have this - Hole inside you?
这股复仇的力量正变地越来越强大 欲望也愈发地强烈
And it just gets bigger and bigger and darker and darker?
是的 你要好好利用它
Good. You can use it.
激发你的欲望
Keeps you hungry.
相信我 你的确需要杀戮 那会让你恢复过来
Trust me, there's plenty out there needs killing and this'll help you do it.
迪恩 你所干的并不是犯罪
Dean, it's not a crime to need your job.
- 这里是海里得旅馆 - 你好 埃伦 我是萨姆·温彻斯特
- Harvelle's Roadhouse. - Hey, Ellen, Sam Winchester.
萨姆 听到你的声音真好
Sam, it's good to hear from you.
- 你们都还好吧 - 还好 一切都还不错
- You boys are okay, aren't you? - Yeah. Yeah, everything's fine.
- 我有个问题 - 说
- Got a question. - Yeah, shoot.
你有遇到过一个叫戈登·沃克的家伙吗
You ever run across a guy named Gordon Walker?
- 我认识戈登 - 还有呢
- Yeah, I know Gordon. - And?
他是个不错的猎人 为什么你要问这个
He's a real good hunter. Why you asking, sweetie?
我们碰到他了 我们正和他一起干
We ran into him on a job and we're kind of working with him.
别那样做 萨姆
Don't do that, Sam.
你不是说他是个不错的猎人吗
I thought you said he was a good hunter.
是的 精神医师汉尼拔告诉我关于他的事
And Hannibal Lecter's a good psychiatrist.
他非常危险
Look, he is dangerous to everyone and everything around him.
如果他在干什么 千万别和他混在一起
If he's working on a job, let him handle it, and move on.
- 埃伦 - 不 萨姆
- Ellen - No, Sam.
请听我的 好吗
You just listen to what I'm telling you, okay?
好吧 我知道了
Right, okay.
- 你知道我为什么这么享受生命吗 - 恩
- Know why I love this life? - Hm?
这个世界只有黑和白 没有中间的状态
It's all black and white. There's no maybe.
你找到了恶魔 毁灭它
You find the bad thing, kill it.
大多数人一生在模棱两可两可中生活
See, most people spend their lives in shades of gray.
这个对吗 哪个不行吗
Is this right, is that wrong? Not us.
那不是我们 萨姆不一定同意你的看法 但是
I'm not sure Sammy would agree with you, but…
你弟弟看起来和我们不同
Doesn't seem like your brother's much like us.
我不是说他不对 只是和我们不同
I'm not saying he's wrong, just different.
我和你 我们生来就是做这个的
You and me, we were born to do this.
血液里的东西
It's in our blood.
呼
Wait.
退后 伊利亚
Step back, Eli.
我叫勒诺 我不想伤害你 我只想和你谈谈
My name's Lenore. I'm not gonna hurt you. We just need to talk.
谈谈吗 好啊 来啊
Talk? Yeah, okay.
我得好好集中精力听听你怎么说
But I might have a tough time
还得提防伊利亚的獠牙
paying attention to much besides Eli's teeth.
有我的话在 他不会伤害你
He won't hurt you. You have my word.
你的承诺 哦 不错啊 太谢谢了
Your word? Oh, yeah, great. Thanks.
女士 我无意冒犯 但我以前不是没见过女吸血鬼
No offense, but you're not the first vampire I've met.
我们和其它吸血鬼不同
We're not like the others. We don't kill humans.
我们不杀害人类 也不吸取他们的血液
We don't drink their blood.
我们很久前就没那么做了
We haven't for a long time.
- 你在和我开玩笑吗 - 请注意 在我们面前 你还活着
- What is this, some kind of joke? - Notice you're still alive.
好吧 如果我错了 那请纠正我
Okay, correct me if I'm wrong here
你们不吸取血液 难道不会饿死
but shouldn't you be starving to death?
我们吸牛血
We've found other ways: cattle blood.
这么说来是你们杀掉了那些牛
You're responsible for all the?
其实 那样对我们来说 很恶心
It's not ideal. In fact, it's disgusting.
但可以让我们活着
But allows us to get by.
- 好吧 为什么你们要这么做 - 为了生存
- Okay, why? - Survival.
没有死亡 没有失踪
No deaths, no missing locals…
也不会发生象你们这样的猎人到处来找我们的事情
no reason for people like you to come looking for people like us.
我们是混血种族
We blend in.
我们这个族快灭绝了
Our kind is practically extinct.
实际上来说 我们也不是想象中那样 在食物链的最高端
Turns out we weren't as high up the food chain as we imagined.
为什么要泄露我们的事情给这个杀手
Why are we explaining ourselves to this killer?
- 伊利亚 - 我们以牛血为生
- Eli. - We choke on cows' blood…
因此人们不用担惊受怕
so that none of them suffer.
而今晚 他们杀害了康拉德 喝酒庆祝
Tonight, they murdered Conrad and celebrated.
- 伊利亚 够了 - 是的 伊利亚 够了
- Eli, that's enough. - Yeah, Eli, that's enough.
过去的都让它过去吧
What's done is done.
- 我们今晚离开这个小镇 - 那为什么带我来这里
- We're leaving this town. - Why did you bring me here?
- 和我说这些事 相信我 - 我也不愿意这样对你
- Why are you even talking to me? - Believe me, I'd rather not.
但是我了解你的做事方式 一旦你有了线索
I know your kind. Once you have the scent
你就会追踪到我们
you'll keep tracking us.
我们躲到那里都无济于事 猎手们会发现我们
It doesn't matter where we go. Hunters will find us.
- 你求我们别再追杀你们 - 我们有生存的权利
- You're asking us not to follow? - We have a right to live.
- 我们也没伤害别人 - 好吧 你可以继续口舌生花
- We're not hurting anyone. - Right, so you keep saying.
但是给我个相信你们的理由
But give me one good reason why I should believe you.
那好吧
Fine.
你知道 我要做什么吗
You know what I'm going to do?
我会放了你
I'm going to let you go.
把他带回去 不准动他一根毫毛
Take him back. Not a mark on him.
这是我测绘的最好的图了 虽然很粗糙
This is the best pattern I can establish. It's sketchy at best.
看起来都是它们从小镇的这边过来的
It's all coming from this side of town.
意味着这个巢穴就离这里不远 不是吗
The nest would be around here, right?
是的 我也这么想
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking.
问题是 那里这样的农场有三四十个
Problem is there's 35, 40 farms out there.
我搜查了它们中的一半 没找到任何线索
I've searched about half of them already, but nothing yet.
他们很善于掩盖踪迹
They're covering their tracks real good.
看来我们不得不搜查剩下的一半
Well, I guess we'll just have to search the other half.
几点啦 萨姆还没回来
What time is it? Where is Sam?
车还在外面 散步去了吧
Car's parked outside. Probably went for a walk.
- 看起来他满喜欢逛逛 - 是 他是有点…
- Seems like the take a walk type. - Yeah, he is, but
- 你去那里呢 - 我能单独和你谈谈吗
- Where you been? - Can I talk to you alone?
不介意我耽误你一点时间吧
You mind chilling out for a couple minutes?
迪恩 也许我们得重新考虑这次行动
Maybe we gotta rethink this hunt.
你在说什么 你去那里呢
What are you talking about? Where were you?
- 在它们的巢穴 - 你找到了
- In the nest. - You found it?
他们找到了我 伙计
They found me, man.
你怎么出来的 你杀了几个
How'd you get out? How many did you kill?
一个也没有
None.
- 他们可不会就这么放你走 - 可他们就是这么做了
- They didn't just let you go. - That's what they did.
- 那好 他们在那里 - 我的眼睛给蒙起来了 我不知道
- All right, well, where is it? - I was blindfolded. I don't know.
- 总会知道点什么吧 - 我们经过了镇外的那座桥
- You gotta know something. - We went over that bridge outside of town.
- 也许我们不该去追杀他们 - 为什么不
- Maybe we shouldn't go after them. - Why not
我觉得他们和其他的吸血鬼不同
I don't think they're like other vampires.
- 他们也不杀人 - 你开玩笑吗
- I don't think they're killing people. - You're joking.
那他们怎么活下来 他们算是那门子吸血鬼
Then how do they stay alive or undead, whatever the hell they are?
那些牛 他们依靠动物的血活着
The cattle mutilations. They live off of animal blood.
- 你相信他们的鬼话 - 看看我 迪恩
- And you believed them? - Look at me, Dean.
他们没碰我一下就让我走了
They let me go without a scratch.
所以 你就这么想…
Wait, so you're saying…?
不 伙计 我不信 我不知道他们为什么要你走
No, man. No way. I don't know why they let you go.
我也不关心 我们去找它们 然后动手做事
I don't really care. We find them and we waste them.
为什么
Why?
你又不是没有遇到过吸血鬼 萨姆
What part of "vampires" don't you understand?
如果它是超自然的东西 我们就杀死它 这是我们的职责
If it's supernatural, we kill it. That's our job.
不 迪恩 这不是我们的工作
No, Dean, that is not our job.
我们只是惩罚邪恶的东西
Our job is hunting evil.
如果他们不伤害人类 他们并不坏
And if these things aren't killing people, they're not evil.
他们当然危害人类 他们一直那么做
Of course they're killing people.
他们都是一样的 萨姆 他们并不是人类 好不好
They're all the same, Sam. They're not human, okay?
我们得追杀他们中的每一个
We have to exterminate them.
不 迪恩 我不这么认为 这次的情况不同
No, Dean. I don't think so, all right? Not this time.
戈登跟踪这些吸血鬼一年多了
Gordon's been on those vamps for a year.
- 他了解情况 - 戈登 你相信他
- He knows. - Gordon? You're taking his word for it?
- 是的 - 埃伦说他不是好人
- That's right. - Ellen says he's bad news.
你和埃伦打电话了吗
You called Ellen?
那我就该无条件相信她吗 我们根本就不了解她
And I'm supposed to listen to her? We barely know her.
- 萨姆 我决定和戈登一起去 - 那好吧 戈登把你哄成那样
- No, thanks. I'll go with Gordon. - Because Gordon's such an old friend.
- 你认为我不了解事情的真相吗 - 你在说什么
- You don't think I can see what this is? - What are you talking about
哪个死掉的家伙不过是你对爸爸的死的发泄
He's a substitute for Dad, isn't he?
- 一个可怜的人 - 闭嘴 萨姆
- A poor one. - Shut up, Sam.
- 他的死对你来说就象是在昨天 - 我甚至不想
- He's not even close. Not on his best day. - I'm not even gonna
你脸上装出那副笑容 可我了解
You slap on this fake smile, but I can see through it…
你的感受 迪恩
because I know how you feel, Dean.
爸爸死了 就象一个黑洞 无时不刻在刺痛你的心
Dad's dead, and he left a hole and it hurts so bad you can't take it.
但你不能因为这个 就乱杀无辜
But you can't just fill up that hole with whoever you want to.
那也是对我们心中的老爸的侮辱
It's an insult to his memory.
那好
Okay.
你可以随便打我 来啊 但那不能改变什么
You can hit me all you want. It won't change anything.
我要去那个巢穴
I'm going to that nest.
你不告诉我在那里 没关系 我自己来找
You don't wanna tell me where it is, fine. I'll find it myself.
迪恩
Dean.
戈登
Gordon?
- 他应该出去找他们了吧 - 很可能
- You think he went after them? - Probably.
- 我们得阻止他 - 真的吗 因为我们说过要出手帮他
- We have to stop him. - Really? Because I say we lend a hand.
我连怀疑的权利都没有了吗 你欠我这个
Just give me the benefit of the doubt, would you? You owe me that.
那好 我们走着瞧 我来开车 给我钥匙
Yeah, we'll see. I'll drive. Give me the keys.
他偷走了钥匙
He snaked the keys.
我都不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我才刚刚把它修好
I just fixed her up too.
那么 你就只记得那座桥了吗
The bridge, is that all you got?
从他们的农场到达桥那只需要四分半钟
The bridge was four and a half minutes from their farm.
- 你怎么知道 - 我心里记着数
- How do you know? - I counted.
出了农场左转 然后 右转上了条泥土路
They took a left out of the farm, then turned right onto a dirt road.
沿着开了两分钟 爬了点小坡
Followed that for two minutes, slightly uphill.
然后右急转 我们就到了桥边
Then took another quick right and we hit the bridge.
你还真不懒啊
You're good.
虽然你这家伙老是惹来麻烦
A monster pain in the ass…
但不得不说你还是很厉害
but you're good.
- 拿去放在卡车里 谢谢 - 我们不能就这么离开
- In the truck, thank you. - We can't leave like this.
勒诺 听我说 我们要留下来 和他们战斗
Lenore, listen to me. We need to stay and fight.
他们也是我的朋友们 我的家人 伊利亚
They were my friends too, Eli. My family.
我不是说这个 这是自卫 反击或者被杀
That's not what I'm talking about.This is self defense.Kill or be killed.
他们死了就不能伤害我们
They can't hunt us if they're dead.
杀害那三个猎人不会解决任何问题
Killing those three wouldn't solve anything.
会有更多的猎人来找我们 我们远远少于他们
There's more where they came from. We're outnumbered.
我们只能这么做
This is all we can do.
- 尝试和他们沟通 说服 - 你不可能说服他们
- Try and reason with - You can't reason with these people.
他们始终还是要杀掉我们的
They're gonna kill us all anyway.
我们至少能和他们同归于尽
We should at least take a few of them with us.
我不会放弃希望的
I'm not giving up hope.
如果我们能改变 为什么他们不能接受呢
If we can change, they can change.
去镇里集合其他人
Now, go into town and gather the others.
日出前我们出发
We leave before sunrise.
死人的血液 婊子
Dead man's blood, bitch.
- 萨姆 迪恩 进来啊 - 戈登 怎么回事
- Sam, Dean, come on in. - Hey, Gordon, what's going on?
我在用死人的血液在折磨她
Just poisoning Lenore here with some dead man's blood.
她会交代出其他人的 不是吗
She's gonna tell us where all her friends are.
- 想来试试吗 - 听着 伙计
- Wanna help? - Look, man
拿把刀来
Grab a knife.
我刚想从另外一只手开始我的游戏
I was just about to start in on the fingers.
喔 喔 喔 喔 这让人起鸡皮疙瘩
Whoa, hey, let's all just chill out, huh?
- 我早就没感觉了 - 戈登 放下手里的刀
- I'm completely chill. - Gordon, put the knife down.
看起来萨姆看不下去了哦
Sounds like it's Sammy that needs to chill.
放开她 好吗
Just step away from her, all right?
你是对的
You're right.
我套不出什么东西
I'm wasting my time here.
这个婊子嘴巴硬得很
This bitch will never talk.
也许让她摆脱痛苦是最好的办法
Might as well put her out of her misery.
这刀我刚磨过 对她来说也算是仁慈了
I just sharpened it, so it's completely humane.
- 戈登 我要放开她 - 你不能那么做
- Gordon, I'm letting her go. - You're not doing a damn thing.
嘿 嘿 戈登 我们来聊聊好吗
Hey, hey, hey. Gordon, let's talk about this.
有什么好说的 就象我说的 黑白中间没有灰色
What's there to talk about? It's like I said, Dean, no shades of gray.
是的 我听你说过
Yeah, I hear you.
- 我也知道你的感受 - 是吗
- And I know how you feel. - Do you?
杀死你妹妹的吸血鬼是该死 但是… 。-
The vampire that killed your sister deserved to die. But this
杀死我的妹妹
Killed my sister?
那个邪恶的吸血鬼并没有那么做 他感染了她
That filthy fang didn't kill my sister. It turned her.
让她也成为了吸血鬼中的一员
Made her one of them.
我追查着她的下落 也亲手结果了她
So I hunted her down and I killed her myself.
- 你做了什么 - 那不再是我的妹妹了
- You did what? - Wasn't my sister anymore.
她根本不是人类 我没有犹豫
It wasn't human. I didn't blink.
您们也不应该犹豫 所以 其实你是了解事实的
Neither would you. So you knew all along, then?
你知道他们不杀害人类 你知道他们没有杀任何人
You knew about the vampires. You knew they weren't killing anyone.
你知道那些牛的死因 只是你根本不关心这个
You knew about the cattle, and you just didn't care.
关心什么
Care about what?
吸血鬼们突然变成了好人
A nest of vampires suddenly acting nice?
除了吸食人类的血液外还做点其它的事情
Taking a little time out from sucking people…
我们就得放过他们 相信我
and we're supposed to buy that? Trust me.
他们根本没有改变
Doesn't change what they are.
我能证明给你看
And I can prove it.
放开他
Let him go.
- 马上 - 放松点
- Now! - Relax.
如果想杀他 他早就没命了
If I wanted to kill him, he'd already be on the floor.
只是让你们了解真相
Just making a little point.
啊 啊 啊
Hey.
她和其它吸血鬼有什么不同吗
You think she's so different?
还想救她吗 看看她现在这个样子
Still wanna save her? Look at her.
他们都是一样的
They're all the same.
邪恶 渴望血液
Evil, bloodthirsty.
不 不要 不要
No. No.
你听到了没 戈登
You hear her, Gordon?
不 不要这么做
No. No.
我们停止吧
We're done here.
- 萨姆 带她出去 - 好的
- Sam, get her out of here. - Yeah.
我帮你
I've got you.
戈登
Gordon…
我想我们有点事要谈
I think you and I got some things to talk about.
别拦着我
Get out of my way.
- 对不起 - 其实你也不想保护她
- Sorry. - You're not serious.
我也很难相信这一切 但当我了解了真相
I'm having a hard time believing it
我知道该怎么做
But I know what I saw.
你想对那些吸血鬼做什么 得先过我这关
If you want those vampires, you gotta go through me.
那好吧
Fine.
你在做什么 伙计 你在保护一个吸血鬼
What are you doing, man? You're doing this for a fang?
醒醒 迪恩 我们是在一条战线上的
Come on, Dean. We're on the same side here.
去你的 你这个虐待狂
I don't think so, you sadistic bastard.
你不会象你的弟弟那样 你是和我一样的杀手
You're not like your brother. You're a killer. Like me.
哦 对不起了
Oh, sorry.
你知道吗
You know…
我可能象你
I might be like you…
但也可能不是
and I might not.
现在你才是那个绑着动不了的家伙
But you're the one tied up right now.
我错过了什么吗
I miss anything?
哦 没什么
Not much.
- 勒诺没事了吧 - 是的
- Lenore get out okay? - Yeah.
他们都没事
All of them did.
我想我们的工作做完了
Then I guess our work here is done.
感觉怎么样啊 戈登
How you doing, Gordy?
不服气吗
You gotta tinkle yet?
那好吧
All right.
轻松点
Well, get comfy.
三天后 我们会打电话叫人来 放开你
We'll call someone in two or three days, have them come out, untie you.
走吧 迪恩
Ready to go, Dean?
等等
Not yet.
我想 我还是说句再见吧
I guess this is goodbye.
嘿 真心的告别
Well, it's been real.
好啦 这下终于舒坦了
Okay. I'm good now.
走吧
We can go.
- 萨姆 - 恩
- Sam. - Yeah?
来 打我一下
Clock me one.
- 什么 - 来 快来
- What? - Come on. Come on.
我不会还手的 来啊
I won't even hit you back. Let's go.
不
No.
来啊 痛快点 随你 来啊
Let's go. You get a freebie. Hit me. Come on.
你现在灰头土脸的 迪恩
You look like you just went 12 rounds with a block of cement, Dean.
以后我再还你这一下
I'll take a rain check.
我真希望我们从没做过这个 从没发现这些
I wish we never took this job. It's jacked everything up.
你想说什么
What do you mean?
想想我们的生活 我们猎杀的种种经历
Think about the hunts we went on, our whole lives.
- 恩 - 如果我们杀错了
- Okay. - What if we killed things…
你知道吗 爸爸一直教育我们那样做
that didn't deserve killing? I mean, the way Dad raised us
迪恩 在妈妈死后
Dean, after what happened to Mom…
- 爸爸已经做到最好了 - 我明白
- …Dad did the best he could. - I know he did.
但也许他并不那么完美
But the man wasn't perfect.
他教导我们的方式 痛恨所有的鬼魂
And the way he raised us to hate those things.
我的确也是那么觉得 我坚信
And, man, I hate them. I do.
我在伐木场杀掉那个吸血鬼的时候
When I killed that vampire at the mill…
我没有怎么想 我甚至喜欢那种杀戮的感觉
I didn't even think about it. Hell, I even enjoyed it.
可你放过了勒诺
You didn't kill Lenore.
是的 但是我的本能告诉我
No, but every instinct told me to.
我该动手杀她 我想杀掉她 消灭他们全部
I was gonna kill her. I was gonna kill them all.
是的 可是你没那么做
Yeah, Dean, but you didn't.
这是事实
And that's what matters.
是的
Yeah.
因为你对我来说是个大麻烦
And because you're a pain in my ass.
我想 对你来说 可能得一直接受我这个麻烦下去了
I guess I might have to stick around and be a pain in the ass, then.
谢谢你
Thanks.
别客气
Don't mention it.